A Finding Aid to the Douglas Leigh Papers, 1903-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leigdoug
Archives of American Art
Douglas Leigh Papers
1903-1999
AAA.leigdoug
Archives of American Art
17.8 Linear feet
The collection measures 17.8 linear feet and dates from 1903 to 1999 (bulk 1924-1992) and documents the career of advertising designer and executive Douglas Leigh. Found are 83 volumes of publicity scrapbooks that contain mostly photographs, clippings, printed materials, and scattered letters, drawings, and blueprints. Also included are professional correspondence; photographs of project installations, aerial advertising, and entertainers; plaques and awards received by Leigh; and printed material, which includes clippings, press kits, advertising materials, designs and original sketches for projects by Leigh. The material reflects Leigh's continuously imaginative use of a wide range of media in promoting his clients' products. Among the projects/campaigns represented are 7up, Airships (Tydol, Flying Red Horse, MGM, Wonder Bread and others), Allied Chemical Tower, Amoco, BlueCross-Blue Shield, Camel cigarettes, Coca-Cola, EPOK, Eveready, Flamingo Frozen Foods, Four Roses Whiskey, Fram Oil Filters, Helmsley Building, Old Gold Cigarettes, Pan Am Building, Pepsi-Cola, R. J. Reynolds, Schaefer Beer, Spectaculars, Stag Beer, Times Tower Building, and Wilson Whiskey.
Douglas Leigh
Biographical Note
Douglas Leigh was born in Anniston, Alabama, in 1907. After graduating from the University of Florida in 1928, he began his career as a salesman for the General Outdoor Advertising Company of Atlanta, Georgia. He moved to New York City in 1930 and developed his ideas for animated and illuminated advertising signs primarily in the vicinity of Times Square. He established his own advertising company, Douglas Leigh, Inc., in 1933 and created the popular Camel Cigarette billboard that featured a man's face exhaling smoke rings over Broadway.
Dubbed "The Man Who Lit Up New York" in his New York Times obituary, he was responsible for festooning Broadway with miles of spectacular electrical and animated signs, such as a steaming coffeepot, a winking penguin on a cake of ice for Kool cigarettes, and the giant Camel sign that puffed smoke rings from a Times Square sign from 1941 and 1967. These effects led to creating animated billboards, an innovation called the Leigh-EPOK animated, billboards matrix display, or EPOK. Leigh developed numerous dirigible advertising projects involving both painted logos and networks of lights over the surface of the dirigible. These sequentially-timed lights caused dramatic animated effects against the night sky.
Leigh was also a pioneer in the illumination of city skylines and buildings and thought of lighting up Manhattan's skyscrapers, beginning with the Empire State Building, in 1976 and continuing with the lighting and gilding of the Con Edison Building, the Helmsley Building, and the Crown Building. This idea was adopted by many other cities, including Cincinnati, Atlanta, Orlando, Miami, New Orleans, and Baltimore with Leigh traveling there to supervise the final installation. Leigh was also involved with numerous urban improvement and renewal projects.
Leigh's career continued into the 1990's, and he died in 1999.
Scope and Content Note
The collection measures 17.8 linear feet and dates from 1903 to 1999 (bulk 1924-1992) and documents the career of advertising designer and executive Douglas Leigh. Found are 83 volumes of publicity scrapbooks that contain mostly photographs, clippings, printed materials, and scattered letters, drawings, and blueprints. Also included are professional correspondence; photographs of project installations, aerial advertising, and entertainers; plaques and awards received by Leigh; and printed material, which includes clippings, press kits, advertising materials, designs and original sketches for projects by Leigh. The material reflects Leigh's continuously imaginative use of a wide range of innovative media in promoting his clients' products.
Among the projects and campaigns represented in the papers are 7up, Airships (Tydol, Flying Red Horse, MGM, Wonder Bread and others), Allied Chemical Tower, Amoco, BlueCross-Blue Shield, Camel cigarettes, Coca-Cola, EPOK, Eveready, Flamingo Frozen Foods, Four Roses Whiskey, Fram Oil Filters, Helmsley Building, Old Gold Cigarettes, Pan Am Building, Pepsi-Cola, R. J. Reynolds, Schaefer Beer, Spectaculars, Stag Beer, Times Tower Building, and Wilson Whiskey.
The Personal Scrapbooks Series (.06 linear feet) consists of 4 scrapbooks that contain photographs, letters, and printed material that document Douglas Leigh's interaction with family, friends, and colleagues.
The General Scrapbooks Series (4.0 linear feet) consists of 16 scrapbooks containing clippings, miscellaneous printed material, letters, interview transcripts, artwork, photographs, and a metal Tydol pin that document the development of miscellaneous projects by Douglas Leigh and his company.
The Billboard Project Files Series (5.0 linear feet) consists primarily of scrapbooks, photographs, and individual product files that document the development of billboard advertising projects.
The Poster Project Files Series (1.6 linear feet) consists of notes, reports, artwork, photographs, miscellaneous printed material, 4 scrapbooks, and individual product files that document the development of poster advertising projects, primarily those used on Railway Express Agency delivery trucks.
The Dirigible Project Files Series (3.7 linear feet) consists of notes, reports, artwork, photographs, miscellaneous printed material, 12 scrapbooks, and individual product files that document the development of dirigible advertising projects involving both painted logos and networks of lights over the surface of the dirigible. These sequentially-timed lights caused dramatic animated effects against the night sky.
The Urban Improvement Project Files Series (2.2 linear feet) consists of photographs, a promotion book, clippings, miscellaneous printed material, 18 scrapbooks, and individual urban improvement project files that document the development of urban improvement projects involving both the construction design of new buildings and the lighting of prominent buildings in New York City and elsewhere.
Arrangement
Scrapbooks within Series 8-13 (Personal Scrapbooks, General Scrapbooks, Billboard Project Files, Poster Project Files, Dirigible Project Files, and Urban Improvement Project Files) have been arranged into as accurate a chronological order as possible. They have been numbered consecutively within each series, and scrapbooks containing material concerning multiple products appear before those concerning individual products.
Oversized materials from various series have been housed in Boxes 6-11, Boxes 12-32 (sols), BV 33, and OV 34, and are noted in the Series Description/Container Listing Section at the appropriate folder title with see also/see references. Additional oversized boxes may be listed with the appropriate series when they contain oversized material from one series only.
The collection has been arranged into 13 series:
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1943-1988 (Box 1, 12; 7 folders)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1924-1999, n.d. (Box 1; 16 folders)
Series 3: Notes, 1941-1997, n.d. (Box 1; 3 folders)
Series 4: Writings by Others, 1962, n.d. (Box 1; 2 folders)
Series 5: Artwork, 1958 (Box 1; 1 folder)
Series 6: Photographs, 1913-1990 (Box 1, 12; .03 linear feet)
Series 7: Printed Material, 1905-1999, n.d. (Box 1; 8 folders)
Series 8: Personal Scrapbooks, 1942-1982 (Box 12-13; .06 linear feet)
Series 9: General Scrapbooks, 1933-1951 (Box 2-5; 4.0 linear feet)
Series 10: Billboard Project Files, 1929-1997 (Box 1, 6-7, 14-25, BV 33; 5.0 linear feet)
Series 11: Poster Project Files, 1943-1963 (Box 7-8, 14; 1.6 linear feet)
Series 12: Dirigible Project Files, 1944-1954 (Box 8-11, 14, 26-28; 3.7 linear feet)
Series 13: Urban Improvement Project Files, 1903-1992 (Box 9, 14, 28-32, OV 34; 2.2 linear feet)
Provenance
The Douglas Leigh papers were donated to the Archives of American Art by Leigh's widow, Elsie M. Leigh, in 2000.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Patrons must use microfilm copy. Original scrapbooks are closed to researchers because of their fragile condition.
Alternative Forms Available
The collection has been filmed on microfilm reels 5840-5848, and is available through interlibrary loan.
Amoco Oil Company.; Coca-Cola Company.; Eveready Battery Company.; Pepsi-Cola Company; R.J. Reynolds Industries.; Seven-Up Company.; Advertising; Airships; Awards; Blueprints; Designers--New York (State)--New York; Interviews; Light in architecture; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Signs and signboards; Sketches; Transcripts
- Biographical Material, 1943-1988; Series 1; (Box 1, 12; 7 folders)
  Scope and Contents note
  Military records document Leigh's service in the U.S. Navy during World War II. Biographical material includes certificates of membership in naval and real estate organizations, and award plaques and certificates. Records are arranged chronologically.
  - Military Service Records, 1943-1954 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Membership Certificates (see also Box 12), 1945-1981 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Award Certificates and Plaques (see also Box 12), 1958-1981 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Bank of New York Medal, 1982 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Greenville High School Hall of Fame Plaque, 1988 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Oversize Membership Certificate, 1945 (Box 12 (sol), Reel 5840)
  - Oversize Award Certificate, 1968 (Box 12 (sol), Reel 5840)
- Correspondence, 1924-1999, n.d.; Series 2; (Box 1; 16 folders)
  The chronologically-arranged correspondence consists of business letters that do not directly relate to a specific project.
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
- Notes, 1941-1997, n.d.; Series 3; (Box 1; 3 folders)
  Notes consist of address lists of business associates, a haphazard collection of clippings entitled "Recognition of Results Obtained," and miscellaneous notes.
  - Address Lists, n.d. (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - "Recognition of Results Obtained,", 1941-1942 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
- Writings by Others, 1962, n.d.; Series 4; (Box 1; 2 folders)
  This series consists of miscellaneous poems and a typescript of remarks by James Felt to the Broadway Association.
  - Miscellaneous Poems, n.d. (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Typescript of Remarks by James Felt, 1962 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
- Artwork, 1958; Series 5; (Box 1; 1 folder)
  Artwork consists of three caricatures of Douglas Leigh by Faruk Alpkurt.
  - Caricatures of Leigh by Faruk Alpkurt, 1958 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
- Photographs, 1913-1990; Series 6; (Box 1, 12; .03 linear feet)
  Photographs are of Douglas Leigh, his boyhood home, family members, and business colleagues. Photographs of Leigh and business colleagues ca. 1939 include a photo of Mickey Rooney. An album contains photographs of office parties at Douglas Leigh, Inc.
  - Photographs of Leigh, His Brother, and Boyhood Home, 1913-1920 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Photographs of Douglas Leigh, ca. 1928-1990; (7 folders) (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Photographs of Leigh's Business Colleagues, 1926 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Photographs of Leigh and Business Colleagues, ca. 1939 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Photographs of Leigh and Business Colleagues, ca. 1945; (2 folders) (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Photographs of Leigh and Business Colleagues, 1964 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Photograph Album of Douglas Leigh, Inc., Office Parties (see also Box 12), 1941-1955 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Oversize Photograph of Leigh and a Colleague, ca. 1964 (Box 12 (sol), Reel 5840)
  - Photograph Album of Douglas Leigh, Inc., Office Parties, 1941-1955 (Box 12 (sol), Reel 5840)
- Printed Material, 1905-1999, n.d.; Series 7; (Box 1; 8 folders)
  Printed material including clippings, brochures, picture postcards, 2 books, a sample book of business stationery, and miscellaneous printed material.
  - Clippings, 1905-1999, n.d.; (15 folders) (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Brochure, "Point of Most Return,", n.d. (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Brochure, "Urban Light Tours Manhattan,", 1985 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Picture Postcards, n.d. (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Color Planning for Business and Industry by Howard Ketcham, 1958 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - The Most Colorful Book Ever!, 1994 (Box 1, Reel 5840)
  - Sample Book of Business Stationery, ca. 1940 (Box 1, Reel 5841)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1925, n.d. (Box 1, Reel 5841)
- Personal Scrapbooks, 1942-1982; Series 8; (Box 12-13; .06 linear feet)
  These personal scrapbooks contain photographs, letters, and printed material documenting Douglas Leigh's interaction with family, friends, and colleagues. One scrapbook contains photographs of Leigh's parents and a skiing holiday. The other scrapbooks record annual business luncheons of the New York Sales Executive Club and the Broadway Association. Personal Scrapbook 3 contains 2 letters and a photograph of John D. Rockefeller III.
  - Personal Scrapbook 1, 1942-1950 (Box 12 (sol), Reel 5841)
  - Personal Scrapbook 2, 1958 (Box 13 (sol), Reel 5841)
  - Personal Scrapbook 3, 1962 (Box 13 (sol), Reel 5841)
  - Personal Scrapbook 4, 1982 (Box 13 (sol), Reel 5841)
- General Scrapbooks, 1933-1951; Series 9; (Box 2-5; 4.0 linear feet)
  The sixteen general scrapbooks found here contain clippings, miscellaneous printed material, letters, interview transcripts, artwork, and photographs documenting the development of miscellaneous projects by Douglas Leigh and his company. General Scrapbook 1 contains a cartoon of Douglas Leigh by Stookie Allen. General Scrapbook 13 contains a metal pin reading "Honorary Tydol Pilot/ Feb 1947."
  - General Scrapbook 1, 1933-1936 (Box 2, Reel 5841)
  - General Scrapbook 2, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Reel 5841)
  - General Scrapbook 3, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Reel 5841)
  - General Scrapbook 4, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Reel 5841-5842)
  - General Scrapbook 5, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 6, 1942 (Box 3, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 7, 1942 (Box 3, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 8, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 9, 1943-1948 (Box 3, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 10, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 11, 1946 (Box 4, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 12, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 13, 1944-1948 (Box 4, Reel 5842)
  - General Scrapbook 14, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Reel 5842-5843)
  - General Scrapbook 15, 1948-1950 (Box 5, Reel 5843)
  - General Scrapbook 16, 1948-1951 (Box 5, Reel 5842)
- Billboard Project Files, 1929-1997; Series 10; (Box 1, 6, 14-25, BV 33; 5.0 linear feet)
  This series consists primarily of 29 scrapbooks and photographs documenting the development of billboard advertising projects, including Leigh's inventions of the Leigh-EPOK Electric Display Board and the Tri-Vision Billboard. Also found are notes, letters, interview transcripts, clippings, miscellaneous printed material, and individual product files. Scrapbooks have been consecutively numbered within this series. Scrapbooks containing material concerning multiple products appear before those concerning individual products. Leigh referred to his billboards as "Spectaculars" because they often were illuminated or displayed mechanized animation.
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged chronologically within each project, with the exception of 10.2: General Photographs, which has been arranged according to subject matter, and 10.5: Individual Billboard Product Files, which has been arranged alphabetically. The series is divided into 5 subseries:
  10.1: General Notes, 1934-1997
  10.2: General Photographs, 1929-1996
  10.3: Leigh-EPOK Electric Display Board, 1966-1993
  10.4: Billboard Scrapbooks for Miscellaneous Products, 1933-1977
  10.5: Individual Billboard Product Files, 1936-1980
  - General Notes, 1934-1997; 10.1
    - Chronologies of Spectaculars, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, n.d. (Box 1, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1934 (Box 1, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1941 (Box 1, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1945 (Box 1, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1946 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1947 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars (see also Box 14), 1948 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars (see also Box 14), 1951 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1952 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1953 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Ideas for Spectaculars, 1954-1985 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Statistics and Photos Concerning Sign Locations, 1945-1997 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Map of Columbus Circle Area (see also Box 14), 1946 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Drawings of Ideas for Spectaculars, 1948 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Drawings of Ideas for Spectaculars, 1951 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize map of Columbus Circle Area, 1946 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
  - General Photographs, 1929-1996; 10.2
    - Ideas for Spectaculars, 1945-1947; (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Buildings in Atlanta, Georgia, 1996, n.d. (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Boardwalk, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1937 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Buildings in Chicago, Illinois, 1958-1973 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - 112 Madison Avenue, Detroit, Michigan, 1945 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Buildings in Los Angeles, California, 1948-1965; (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - New York City skyline, 1959, n.d.; (see also Box 14) (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Times Square, New York City (see also Box 14), 1929-1980; (12 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Columbus Circle, New York City (see also Box 14), 1934-1963; (8 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Sixth Avenue and Radio City, New York City, 1942-1961 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Bryant Park, New York City, 1929-1950 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Wurlitzer Building (120 W 42nd), New York City, 1950-1970 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - 522 Fifth Avenue, New York City, 1955-1961 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - 40 Wall Street, New York City, 1975 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Statue of Liberty, New York City, 1942 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Buildings, New York City, 1940-1970 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous buildings, Brooklyn, New York, 1940-1943 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Buildings, Queens and The Bronx, 1940-1943 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Oakland, California Skyline (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Unidentified U. S. cities, n.d. (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Miscellaneous Foreign Cities (see also Box 14, 1966, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Tri-Vision Billboard Photographs of Fabrication, ca. 1962 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph of Canada Dry Sign, 1947-1949 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph of Chevrolet Sign, 1947-1949 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph of Planters Peanuts Sign, 1947-1949 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph, 2 Views of Times Square, 1950-1959 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photographs of Coca-Cola Sign, 1945 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph of Chevrolet Sign, 1946-1947 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph of Columbus Circle, 1954-1959 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
    - Oversize Photograph of a Building in Moscow, Russia, n.d. (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5843)
  - Leigh-EPOK Electric Display Board, 1966-1993; 10.3
    - Leigh-EPOK Notebook with 5 Photos, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Reel 5843)
    - Animation Inventory Lists, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Reel 5843-5844)
    - Photographs of Signs and Performers, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Brochures About the Leigh-EPOK Sign, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Booklet About the Leigh-EPOK Sign, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
  - Billboard Scrapbooks for Miscellaneous Products, 1933-1977; 10.4
    Billboard Scrapbook 8 includes a photo of Joan Crawford; Billboard Scrapbook 9 includes a photo of cartoonist Otto Soglow; Billboard Scrapbook 10 includes photos of dancers Bill Robinson and the De Marcos; and Billboard Scrapbook 16 includes a photo of Sophia Loren.
    - Billboard Scrapbook 1 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1933-1964 (Box BV 33, Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 2 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1934-1966 (Box 15 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 3 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1937-1966 (Box 15 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 4 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1945-1966 (Box 16 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 5 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1962-1977 (Box 16 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 6 (see also Box 14), 1934-1941; (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 7 (see also Box 14), 1935-1939 (Box 17 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 8, 1936-1937 (Box 17 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Oversize Poster from Billboard Scrapbook 6, 1934-1941 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Oversize Poster from Billboard Scrapbook 7, 1935-1939 (Box 14 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 9, 1938-1947 (Box 18 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 10, 1944-1946 (Box 18 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 11, 1951-1952 (Box 18 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 12, 1950 (Box 19 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 13, 1955-1956 (Box 19 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 14, 1955-1965 (Box 19 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 15, 1961 (Box 19 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 16, 1962 (Box 20 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 17, 1963 (Box 20 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 18, 1966 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 19, 1967 (Box 20 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 20, 1941-1947 (Box 21 (sol), Reel 5844)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 21, 1948-1950 (Box 21 (sol), Reel 5845)
  - Individual Billboard Product Files, 1936-1980; 10.5
    Billboard Scrapbook 25 includes photographs of Broadway performers Joan McCracken, June Havoc, Bambi Linn, and the De Marcos; Wilson Whiskey Billboard Scrapbook 27 includes a photograph of Joan Crawford.
    - Aqua Net Hairspray Photographs, 1936 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Ballantine's Beer Photographs, 1936 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Black Horse Ale Photographs of Sign (see also Box 14), 1944 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - BOAC Airlines Photographs, 1955 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Bond Clothes Photographs (see also Box 14), 1949 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Borden's Instant Coffee Photograph, ca. 1960s (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Braniff Airlines Photograph of Sign Installation, 1964 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Brim Freeze-Dried Coffee Photograph, ca. 1950s (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Bulova Watches Photographs, ca. 1950s (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Camel Cigarettes, Photographs, 1942-1951 (Box 6, Reel 5844)
    - Canada Tourism, Photographs, 1960 (Box 6, Reel 5845)
    - Chevrolet Automobiles, Photographs (see also Box 14), n.d. (Box 7, Reel 5845)